Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 9, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: The Duties of Citizenship, Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Box: 9, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights: Barometer of Democracy, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Author: Edward J. Sparling
  - Item 2: New Threats to American Freedoms, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Author: Robert E. Cushman
- Box: 9, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Teaching the Civil Liberties: A Source Unit, 1941; Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Author: Howard E. Wilson
    Notes: May 1941
- Box: 9, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights and Present Wrongs, 1968; Publication (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Author: Alan Paton
- Box: 9, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights Today, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Author: The American Jewish Committee
- Box: 9, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Legislation Against Discrimination in Canada, 1969; Publication (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Author: Robert William Kerr
- Box: 9, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Human Rights in the United Kingdom, 1963; Publication (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Notes: September 1963
- Box: 9, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: U.S. Observance of International Human Rights Year, 1968, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Author: Committee on Foreign Affairs
    Notes: August 11 and 17, 1966
- Box: 9, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The 1966 Kentucky Civil Rights Act: An Explanation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Author: Commonwealth of Kentucky
- Box: 9, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Violence in Peekskill, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Notes: August 27 & September 4, 1949
- Box: 9, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The People Take the Lead: A Record of Progress in Civil Rights 1948 to 1959, Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Author: National Labor Service
    Notes: January 1959
  - Item 2: Your Civil Rights: A Handbook for Trade Union Members and Organizers, Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Program for the Bill of Rights 1946, Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Notes: January 1946
  - Item 4: The Supreme Court and Civil Liberties: How Far Has the Court Protected the Bill of Rights?, 1945; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Author: Osmond K. Fraenkel
    Notes: October 1945
  - Item 5: Our Uncertain Liberties, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Notes: August 1948
  - Item 6: Liberty on the Homefront: In the Fourth Year of War, 1945; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: In the Shadow of Fear, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Post-War Hysteria, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: A National Program for Civil Rights, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Notes: April 1948
  - Item 10: What Do You Mean, Free Speech?, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: In Times of Challenge, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: From War to Peace, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Notes: July 1946
  - Item 13: Nations in Nightshirts, 1937; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Notes: December 8, 1937
- Box: 9, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights in the United States in 1949, Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: American Jewish Congress, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - Item 2: Report of the Civil Liberties Committee, 1938; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: National Lawyers Guild: Oregon Chapter
    Notes: May 24, 1938
  - Item 3: Let's Look at Ourselves: A Brief Guide for Conducting a Community Audit, Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: National Citizens' Council on Civil Rights
  - Item 4: Civil Rights in the United States in 1948, Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: National Associtaion for the Advancement of Colored People, American Jewish Congress
  - Item 5: These Rights are Ours to Keep, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: Jerome Ellison
  - Item 6: To Secure These Rights, Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: The President's Committee on Civil Rights
  - Item 7: Safeguarding Our Civil Liberties, 1943; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Progress in Civil Rights, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Author: John W. Gibson
    Notes: January 18, 1948
- Box: 9, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights: Excerpts from the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report, Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Author: United States Commission on Civil Rights
  - Item 2: Some Questions and Answers on the Civil Rights Bill, Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Author: Leadership Conference on Civil Rights
  - Item 3: Guide to the Civil Rights Act, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Freedom of the Mind, 1962; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Author: William O. Douglas
  - Item 5: Security, Civil Liberties, and Unions, 1956; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Author: American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations
    Notes: July 1956
  - Item 6: The Equal Employment Opportunity Law, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Notes: July 2, 1964
  - Item 7: Civil Rights Act of 1966, Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. House of Representatives
    Notes: July 14, 1966
  - Item 8: Civil Rights Act of 1966, Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Notes: June 30, 1966
  - Item 9: Civil Rights Under Federal Programs, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights
- Box: 9, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Civil Rights Story, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Author: Harry Fleischman
  - Item 2: Some Questions and Answers on the Civil Rights Bill, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Author: Lee Metcalf
    Notes: April 11, 1964
  - Item 3: Civil Rights Acts of 1957, 1960, 1964 and Voting Rights Act of 1965, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Notes: October 27, 1966
  - Item 4: Civil Rights: Message from the President of the United States Relative to Racial Discrimination in Housing, Education, Voting Etc., and Recommendations for Legislation, 1967; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Author: U.S. President Johnson
    Notes: February 16, 1967
- Box: 9, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Civil Liberties and Civil Rights in the United States Today, 1956; Publication (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Box: 9, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Bill of Rights and the States, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Author: William J Brennan
  - Item 2: Civil Rights Act of 1963, Publication (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Notes: November 20, 1963
- Box: 9, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights Under Federal Programs: An Analysis of Title IV of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, 1968; Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: The Equal Employment Opportunity Law: Title VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Author: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc.
    Notes: July 3, 1964
  - Item 3: Public Law 88-352, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: What's Ahead for Employers Under the Civil Rights Act?, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Author: Eugene Adams Keeney
    Notes: October 21, 1965
- Box: 9, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Specimen Questions from U.S. Civil Service Examinations, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Occupational Structure Established Under the Classification Act of 1949, Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Notes: October 28, 1949
  - Item 3: The Merit System in 1947, Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Author: National Civil Service League
- Box: 9, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Government of Vietnam Civil Service System in April 1969, Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: U.S. Agency for International Development
  - Item 2: First Phase Report of the Public Employment Career Development Program, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: The New Jersey Office of Economic Opportunity
    Notes: December 1966
  - Item 3: Lestungsentlohnung Im Offentlichen Betrieb, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: Gabriel Plattner
  - Item 4: Centralforeningen for Fagorganiserede Arbejdere Under Forsvarministeriet, 1967; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: Norrebros Bogtrykkeri
    Language: Danish.
  - Item 5: Legislacion Vigente Sobre Administration de Personal de la Republica de Panama, 1962; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: Republica de Panama
  - Item 6: What You Should Know As an Employee of the Province of New Brunswick, 1967; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: Civil Service Commission of New-Brunswick
    Language: English; French.
  - Item 7: The Civil Service, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: Ian Finlay
  - Item 8: The Civil Services of North America, 1969; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Item 9: Public Employment in California, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Author: Orville F. Poland
  - Item 10: Future Developments in the Public Service of Uganda, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Box: 9, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: State of Alaska Personnel Rules, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Author: Alaska Department of Administration
- Box: 9, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Civil Service and the Administrative Career in Columbia, 1963; Publication (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Author: Escuela Superior de Administration Publica
    Language: Spanish; English; French.
- Box: 9, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: When You Take a Civil Service Test, 1955; Publication (Box 9, Folder 40)
    Author: Dorothy W. Otten
    Notes: April 1955
- Box: 9, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Organisation of the Scientific Civil Service, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Box: 9, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: A Policy for Employee-Management Cooperation in the Federal Service, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Author: U.S. President's Task Force on Employee-Management Relations in the Federal Service
    Notes: November 30, 1961
  - Item 2: Employee-Management Cooperation in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Author: The White House
  - Item 3: Guide to Standards of Conduct for Federal-Employee Unions, Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Item 4: Important Events Relating to the Federal Government Labor Movement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Item 5: Organized Public Employee Relations, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Author: University of California Los Angeles
  - Item 6: Union Recognitions in Non-Appropriated Fund Activities of the Department of Defense, 1967; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Notes: November 1967
  - Item 7: Unionization of Federal Employees? The Workingman's View on this and Other Issues, 1962; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Item 8: Unions are Here to Stay: A Guide for Employee-Management Relations in the Federal Service, 1962; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Author: Ann Holland
- Box: 9, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Public Employees and Employee Organizations, Publication (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Author: American Public Works Association
  - Item 2: A Decade of AFL Unionism in State, County and Municipal Service, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Notes: September 1946
  - Item 3: Relationships with Employee Groups or Organizations in the Army Service Forces, 1944; Publication (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Author: Army Service Forces
    Notes: September 25, 1944
- Box: 9, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Independent State and Local Public Employee Associations in California, 1963, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Notes: March1965
- Box: 9, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: The New Militancy of Public Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Author: California Institute of Governmental Studies
  - Item 2: Massachusetts Civil Service: How it Works and Where it Has Failed, 1966; Publication (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Author: Massachusetts Taxpayers Foundation
- Box: 10, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: Montana Legislative Council
- Box: 10, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 1965 Statistical Data on Public Employments in New York State, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Author: New York State Department of Civil Service
- Box: 10, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: You and Your State Job, 1947; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Merit System and The Constitution, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: Civil Service Reform Association
  - Item 3: Careers for College Graduates in New York State Government, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: New York State Civil Service Commission
  - Item 4: Civil Service Administration in the Empire State, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 30, 1953
  - Item 5: Application of the Labor Law to Municipal Corporations, 1954; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 25, 1954
  - Item 6: Civil Service Administration in the Empire State, 1950; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Box: 10, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Rules, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: Oregon Civil Service Commission
- Box: 10, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Revision of Pension Rules and Rates, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Author: Government of East Pakistan
    Notes: September 2, 1966
- Box: 10, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 1967 Idaho Public Employee Retirement System Law, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Author: Idaho Public Employee Retirement Board
- Box: 10, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Laws Governing the Employees' Retirement System of the State of Maryland, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: State of Maryland Employees' Retirement System
- Box: 10, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Retirement Allowances Paid to Formar State and Local Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Author: Massachusetts Federation of Taxpayers Associations
- Box: 10, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of Employee Retirement Systems Interim Commission, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Author: State of Minnesota Legislature
- Box: 10, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Public Employees' Retirement Act of New Mexico, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Author: New Mexico Public Employees' Retirement Board
    Notes: October 1967
- Box: 10, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Retirement Credit for Service with the State of North Carolina, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
    Notes: April 26, 1966
- Box: 10, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Statstjanstemannens Pensioner, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: TCO:s Statstjanstemannasektion
- Box: 10, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Retirement, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Notes: July 10 and 11, 1969
  - Item 2: Government Counterclaims Against Amounts Due from Civil Service Retirement and Disability Fund, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 9, 1965
  - Item 3: Civil Service Retirement Annuities, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Notes: August 12 and 13, 1965
  - Item 4: Your Retirement System: Questions and Answers Concerning the Federal Civil Service Retirement Law, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Liberalize Eligibility for Cost-of-Living Increases in Retirement Annuities, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Notes: May 3, 1971
  - Item 6: Comprehensive Tax Guide to U.S. Civil Service Retirement Benefits, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Author: U.S. Department of the Treasury
    Notes: April 1974
- Box: 10, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Proposed Revision of Law Governing Financing of Salary Costs of Retired Civil Service Annuitants Reemployed by Federal Agencies, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. General Accounting Office
  - Item 2: Clarifying Annuity Increase Legislation, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 25, 1965
  - Item 3: Special Report of the Board of Actuaries on the Valuation of the Civil Service Retirement System as of June 30, 1958, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: July 1959
  - Item 4: Survey of Income of Civil Service Annuitants, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Civil Service Retirement Annuities, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: September 13, 1972
  - Item 6: Civil Service Retirement Financing, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 26, 1968
  - Item 7: Improved Retirement Financing, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 19, 1967
  - Item 8: Retirement Credit for Federal-State Services, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 24, 1966
  - Item 9: Retirement, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: May 6 and 7, 1968
  - Item 10: Civil Service Retirement Annuity Increases, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Senate
    Notes: August 30, 1965
  - Item 11: Survivor Annuities with Respect to Reemployed Annuitants, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: September 28, 1966
  - Item 12: A Survey of State and Local Government Retirement Systems, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Box: 10, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Amending Further the Civil Service Retirement Act, 1946; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Notes: May 27, 1946
- Box: 10, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Retirement of Constitutional Offices and Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Author: Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Purchases and Supply
- Box: 10, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Zambia Civil Service: Contributory Pensions, Chapter 48 of the Laws, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Author: Republic of Zambia
- Box: 10, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management, 1949; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 10, 1949
  - Item 2: Organization, Functions, and Relative Costs of Personnel Offices, 1948; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Notes: June 4, 1948
- Box: 10, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A Policy for Employee-Management Cooperation in the Federal Service, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: The President's Task Force on Employee-Management Relations in the Federal Service
  - Item 2: Personnel Practices Relating to Blue Collar Workers, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: Public Personnel Association
  - Item 3: State Employee Relations Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: State of Michigan Civil Service Commission
    Notes: December 1, 1964
  - Item 4: Recruitment and Selection in the Public Service of Developing Countries, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Personnel Administration in North Carolina Cities, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: Donald Hayman
  - Item 6: The Federal Executive Service, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: February 3, 1971
  - Item 7: Guide to Personnel Assistance for State and Local Governments Institutes of Higher Education, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: June 1972
  - Item 8: Summary of Selected IPA Products, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 1974
  - Item 9: A Policy for Employee-Management Cooperation in the Federal Service, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: President's Task Force on Employee-Management Relations in the Federal Service
  - Item 10: The Merit System in Massachusetts: A Study of Public Personnel Adminstration in the Commonwealth, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: League of Women Voters of Massachusetts
- Box: 10, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement System, 1975; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Notes: July 1975
- Box: 10, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Retirement Act, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Notes: October 11, 1962
  - Item 2: Survivor Annuities with Respect to Reemployed Annuitants, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Notes: October 6, 1966
  - Item 3: Clarifying Certain Civil Service Retirement Provisions: Report, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Notes: April 9, 1965
  - Item 4: An Act to Preserve the Benefits of the Civil Service Retirement Act, the Federal Employees' Group Life Insurance Act of 1954, and the Federal Employees Health Benefits Act of 1959 for Congressional Employees Receiving Certain Congressional Staff Fellowshi, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Notes: March 30, 1966
  - Item 5: Amending the Civil Service Retirement Act, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Notes: February 18, 1966
- Box: 10, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Federal Employees' Salary Rates, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Author: Army Times Publishing Company
    Notes: July 18, 1966
  - Item 2: Tuition Reimbursement and Educational Leave, Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Box: 10, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Service Rating Comments, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Author: Michigan Civil Service Commission
- Box: 10, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Fellowship and Internship Opportunities for Federal Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Box: 10, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Productivity in State and Local Government, 1973; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Author: National Commission on Productivity
    Notes: July 1973
  - Item 2: Fedaral Career Directory: A Guide for College Students, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Investment for Tomorrow, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Author: U.S. Presidential Task Force on Career Advancement
  - Item 4: Manpower for Government -- A Decade's Forecast, 1958; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Author: Eli Ginzberg and James K. Anderson
  - Item 5: Federal Workforce Outlook: Fiscal Years 1965-1968, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Efforts to Employ Disadvantaged Persons in the Federal Government, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Notes: April 17, 1972
  - Item 7: So, Mr. Mayor, You Want to Improve Productivity, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Author: National Commission on Productivity and Work Quality in Cooperation with the Ford Foundation
  - Item 8: Variation of the 40-Hour Workweek, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Notes: June 9, 1965
  - Item 9: Variation of the 40-Hour Workweek of Federal Employees for Educational Purposes, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Notes: June 14, 1966
  - Item 10: Working for the U.S.A., 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Box: 10, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Working for the U.S.A., 1952; Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Futures in Federal Government, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)